Email: mp8561295@gmail.com

Carrier objective

To emerge as a result oriented performance through continuous assimilation of knowledge and accumulation of skills while serving efficiently to the requirements of the organization and contributes to its growth and success.

Education

I am Bachelor of Arts Graduate from MANGALORE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGICAL SCIENCE at 2013

Summary of experience:

I am young, energetic Person possessing excellent communication and computer skills with a keen interest in Internet technologies. I am working with the leading Banking organization wherein I have gained good experience in both front-end and back-end operations related to customer service & sales with a total experience of 6 years 9 months on company roles.

1. Professional Experience:

Name of the Company : FINNEX BUSINESS SERVICES PVT LTD

Location : BANGALORE
Designation : FIELD EXECUTIVE

Period of association : 2^{ND} -NOV-2016 to 19^{TH} -DEC-2018

Job Responsibilities:

- Implemented sales guidelines and standards across departments.
- Generated sales ideas.
- Assisted advertising departments and formulated competitive analysis reports.
- Handled online promotions and coordinated with customers about latest offers.
- Executed sales strategies and handled banking sales.

2. Professional Experience:

Name of the Company : IDFC FIRST BANK (Team capital --9th Jan 2019 to 6th Feb

2020, Buzzworks business services pvt ltd 7th Feb 2020

to 22nd May 2023)

Location : BANGALORE Designation : Sales officer

Period of association : 9th Jan 2019 to 21st May 2023



Job Responsibilities:

- Handled request for information on personal loan and services.
- Maintains quality service by establishing and enforcing organization standards.
- Coordinated with customers on personal loan requirements.
- Develop strategies for more effective sales, both individually and as part of a team
- Trained and the Lead of the Five juniors.
- Marketed bank products and programs.
- Collaborate with team members to achieve better results.
- Promote specific products as directed by upper management.
- Developing and sustaining long-lasting relationships with customers.
- Managed customers' questions.
- Maintain a good relationship with clients manage their concerns and queries.

3. Professional Experience:

Name of the Company : IDFC FIRST BHARAT LTD

Location : BANGALORE Designation : Sales officer

Period of association : 22nd May to till date

Personal Details:

Name : MANOJ M

Father's name : MAHADEVA SHETTY

Date of Birth : 12/01/1995 Marital Status : Un-married

Languages Known : Telugu, English, Kannada and Hindi

Address : T narasipura thalluk dodda bagilu grama doddabailu

Mysore Karnataka pin 571120

Contact Number : 9071040711

E-mail ID : mp8561295@gmail.com

Date:

Bangalore MANOJ M

